

Larry Gonzales

larrygonzales727@gmail.com | 210-279-5731 | larryg.tech | Github.com/larryg727 | linkedin.com/in/larrygonzales-dev

Summary

- * Full-stack JavaScript and Java developer with a strong passion for programming.
- * Transitioning from eight years in the appliance repair industry which utilized problem solving skills and adaptability.
- * Excited and eager to learn new things to push my abilities and overcome challenges of solving complex problems as a valued member of a great development team.

Recent Projects

Capstone Project - July 2017

This is where i will briefly describe how awesome my capstone project is, and describe my main roles and launguages used in developing it.

Adlister - June 2017

A web app that allows users to create accounts and view, create, and browse ads created by users. By integrating the MySQL database I was able to store, update and pull user account and ad info to create this dynamic web app.

Java | MySQL | JSP | JSTL HTML | CSS | Bootstrap

Texas Affordable Appliance - June 2017

A project to help a local appliance repair company build a web presence with a website. I built this site from scratch including all content and images.

HTML | CSS | JavaScript
JQuery | Bootstrap

Simple Simon - May 2017

A Simon memory game clone that is mobile responsive and implements features like high-score and standard and reverse levels. All logic and animations for game are written in Javascript and JQuery.

JavaScript | JQuery

HTML | CSS

Skills

Frontend

JavaScript | JQuery | React.JS HTML | CSS | Bootstrap

Backend

Java | MySQL PHP | Spring Framework

Additional

JSON | AJAX API Integration | Git Mobile Responsiveness

Personal

Fast Learner | Driven
Self-starter | Knowledge-seeker

Experience

Allstar Appliance Repair, April 2016- March 2017 - Service Technician

- * Utilized problem solving and logic skills to properly diagnose and repair residential appliances.
- * Document services and properly quote customers for services needed and rendered.
- * Maintain up to date knowledge of technical data and issues of specific industry technoligies.

Appliance Parts Depot, October 2014- April 2016 - Customer Service Rep.

- * Guided customers though diagnosis and repair of appliances utilizing technical knowledge and problem solving skills.
- * Sold over \$60,000 monthly of appliance parts and accesories.
- * Maintained customer relations with service companies utilizing customer service skills.

Classic Appliance Repair, August 2013- October 2014 - Service Technician

- Utilized problem solving and logic skills to properly diagnose and repair residential appliances.
- * Document services and properly quote customers for services needed and rendered.
- * Maintain up to date knowledge of technical data and issues of specific industry technoligies.

Education

Codeup, March- July 2017

Completed an immersive fullstack program with over 536 hours of instruction and development of projects.

Capella University, 2015- 2016

Completed 24 credit hours towards the Information Technology degree program with a major in web-development.